<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ryan brushett</title>
    <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ryan brushett</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 12:59:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/advent-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 12:59:17 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/advent-2023/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: I probably won&amp;rsquo;t stick with advent of code again but I&amp;rsquo;m going to try!&#xA;I once eagerly declared my intention to finish Advent of Code and then didn&amp;rsquo;t. I&amp;rsquo;m going to be a bit more realistic about my expectations this year.&#xA;This is what I said in my follow-up on accountability&amp;hellip;&#xA;Next year I hope to do better, get farther, be faster, etc. I&amp;rsquo;ll use Ruby again! And it&amp;rsquo;ll be a lot of fun again!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent Update</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/advent-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 21:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/advent-two/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: I never stuck with Advent of Code and I think that&amp;rsquo;s mostly OK.&#xA;As a follow up to my eager and excited post about Advent of Code&amp;hellip; I was definitely getting ahead of myself haha. I&amp;rsquo;ve still never completed a full advent of code.&#xA;On learning stuff I said the thing I&amp;rsquo;d set out to learn is &amp;ldquo;finishing Advent of Code&amp;rdquo; but I actually learned a lot, even using a language I&amp;rsquo;m pretty handy with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/advent-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 22:36:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/advent-one/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: So far so good&amp;hellip; follow along on Github!&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m probably getting ahead of myself by writing this but it seems like I might actually be sticking with Advent of Code this year. I&amp;rsquo;ve set myself up for success and maybe this will hold me accountable&amp;hellip;&#xA;On Learning Stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve never completed a full Advent of Code.&#xA;Around October of this year I decided that was probably because I was trying to do too much at once.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Film Work?</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/how-does-film-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 11:27:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/how-does-film-work/</guid>
      <description>I wrote a thing about Pushing Delta 3200 which very lightly skimmed over a lot of actually pretty interesting things. I gave a high-level overview of how I develop a specific black and white film (with a lot about why I do it that way) but I&amp;rsquo;d like to explore some of the technical stuff a bit more. It&amp;rsquo;s a good excuse for me to research these things.&#xA;Seems logical to talk about what film actually is and how it works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing Delta 3200</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/pushing-delta-3200/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:52:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/pushing-delta-3200/</guid>
      <description>Unless you&amp;rsquo;re interested in reading why I like fast film, you can skip to this section for how I actually develop it. That&amp;rsquo;s the part that covers what made me want to write this in the first place. I kept losing my notes so this will actually serve as a long-winded note-to-self.&#xA;If you want to skip to some pictures, see results.&#xA;Historical context Around 2007, I got pretty into photography.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 22:28:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Yeah I might actually use this to write about things.&#xA;(2022-02-03): I&amp;rsquo;ve got so many half-finished drafts that have just been sitting there, neatly tucked away in their own little branches. Maybe I was just never destined to write like this.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
