<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ryan brushett</title>
    <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ryan brushett</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 11:27:09 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Does Film Work?</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/how-does-film-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 11:27:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/how-does-film-work/</guid>
      <description>I wrote a thing about Pushing Delta 3200 which very lightly skimmed over a lot of actually pretty interesting things. I gave a high-level overview of how I develop a specific black and white film (with a lot about why I do it that way) but I&amp;rsquo;d like to explore some of the technical stuff a bit more. It&amp;rsquo;s a good excuse for me to research these things.
Seems logical to talk about what film actually is and how it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pushing Delta 3200</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/pushing-delta-3200/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:52:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/pushing-delta-3200/</guid>
      <description>Unless you&amp;rsquo;re interested in reading why I like fast film, you can skip to this section for how I actually develop it. That&amp;rsquo;s the part that covers what made me want to write this in the first place. I kept losing my notes so this will actually serve as a long-winded note-to-self.
If you want to skip to some pictures, see results.
Historical context Around 2007, I got pretty into photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 22:28:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ryanbrushett.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Yeah I might actually use this to write about things.
(2022-02-03): I&amp;rsquo;ve got so many half-finished drafts that have just been sitting there, neatly tucked away in their own little branches. Maybe I was just never destined to write like this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
